Guide to the Kilpatrick Collection of Cherokee Manuscripts
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Notebook #8: "Medicine Men of the Cherokee"
  - Wadi, Denili (Watt, Daniel). Unidentified, undated (Box 7, Folder 555)
  - Wadi, Denili (Watt, Daniel). Unidentified letter, 1904 July 25 (Box 7, Folder 556)
  - Wadi, Unesdala. "Goingsnake District", undated (Box 7, Folder 557)
  - Letter, community, undated (Box 7, Folder 558)
  - Business letter, undated (Box 7, Folder 559)
  - Letter, unidentified, undated (Box 7, Folder 560)
  - Ledger, names and numbers, undated (Box 7, Folder 561)
  - Nitehawk Stomp Dance, undated (Box 7, Folder 562)
  - Song (Hymn?) 63, undated (Box 7, Folder 563)
  - Bible quotation or sermon, undated (Box 7, Folder 564)
  - Wili, Adonisgi. Letter (Box 7, Folder 565)
  - Unidentified note, 1891 (Box 7, Folder 566)
  - Bible quotation, undated (Box 7, Folder 567)
  - List of names and associated numbers, undated (Box 7, Folder 568)
  - "Covenant" hymn, undated (Box 7, Folder 569)
  - Trumpet, John. Writing practice, undated (Box 7, Folder 570)
  - Historical, undated (Box 7, Folder 571)
  - Ledger, 1923 September 14 (Box 7, Folder 572)
  - Prayer, beginning "nasgino gohi sunale utsatigwo galieligvi", undated (Box 7, Folder 573)
  - Sawny, Jennie. Journal, undated (Box 7, Folder 574)
  - Sawny, Jennie. Letter, undated (Box 7, Folder 575)
  - Kingfisher, Pauline. Letter, undated (Box 7, Folder 576)
  - Song, undated (Box 7, Folder 577)
  - "Bains Kontkof for the Rapid Relief cough" and unidentified Cherokee text, undated (Box 7, Folder 578)
  - Brown, George. Letter to Gray Brothers, 1931 May 1 (Box 7, Folder 579)
  - Love letter, undated (Box 7, Folder 580)
  - "Dunlap's colic remedy for horses and mules" and unidentified Cherokee text, undated (Box 7, Folder 581)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 7, Folder 582)
  - Song, Solfege notation, undated (Box 7, Folder 583)
    English translation of Solfege notation published in Shadow, p. 74-5
  - Letter, unidentified, undated (Box 7, Folder 584)
  - Letter, unidentified, 1925 July 3 (Box 7, Folder 585)
  - Community, letter, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 586)
  - Trumpet, John. Unidentified, undated (Box 7, Folder 587)
  - Prayer, undated (Box 7, Folder 588)
  - Dotsuwa, Seli (Redbird, Seli). Letter, beginning "ayv tsotsuwa gowelvga unelanvhigwono wigisdela", undated (Box 7, Folder 589)
  - Tsugiwisda, Tsowa. Letter to Didalidisgi Wadi, undated (Box 7, Folder 590)
  - Wadi, Henili (Watt, Henry). Business letter beginning "ayvno nasgwo adela digvginedi ugvwali", undated (Box 7, Folder 591)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 7, Folder 592)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 7, Folder 593)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 7, Folder 594)
  - Jumper, Charlie. Note, undated (Box 7, Folder 595)
  - List of names and numbers, undated (Box 7, Folder 596)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 7, Folder 597)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 7, Folder 598)
  - Financial record, undated (Box 7, Folder 599)
  - Financial record, undated (Box 7, Folder 600)
  - Prayer, contains "ka se?dina tsanelanvhi", undated (Box 7, Folder 601)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 7, Folder 602)
  - Ugadoehi, John. Note, undated (Box 7, Folder 603)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 7, Folder 604)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 7, Folder 605)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 7, Folder 606)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 7, Folder 607)
  - Uwedasadi, Dlasani. Financial note, undated (Box 7, Folder 608)
  - Financial note, undated (Box 7, Folder 609)
  - Financial note, undated (Box 7, Folder 610)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 7, Folder 611)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 7, Folder 612)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 7, Folder 613)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 7, Folder 614)
  - Financial note, undated (Box 7, Folder 615)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 7, Folder 616)
  - Journal, 1901 September 15 (Box 7, Folder 617)
- Notebook #9: "Medicine Men of the Cherokee"
  Annotated: "Mostly 19th century"
  - Kilpatrick notebook cover, "9, Medicine Men of the Cherokees (mostly 19th Century)", undated (Box 7, Folder 618)
  - Buck, John. Medical formula, December 3 (Box 7, Folder 619)
    Author identified by note in Jack Kilpatrick's hand.
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 7, Folder 620)
  - Suli, Gugonvdv. Medical formula, 1953 July 3 (Box 7, Folder 621)
  - Doyanisi, Dlanusi. Medical formula, undated (Box 7, Folder 622)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 7, Folder 623)
    Found in proximity: note in Jack Kilpatrick's hand, "Adelagatiya Kanisgawi Coll."
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 7, Folder 624)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 7, Folder 625)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 7, Folder 626)
  - Instructions, undated (Box 7, Folder 627)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 7, Folder 628)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 7, Folder 629)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 7, Folder 630)
  - Note, begins "nvya tsiluya ada", undated (Box 7, Folder 631)
  - Jumper, Agnes Standingdeer. Medical formula, undated (Box 7, Folder 632)
  - Dlanusi, Sigwoya. Medical formula, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 633)
  - Wolf, Scott. Medical formula, undated (Box 7, Folder 634)
    Author (Wolf, Scott) suggested by note in Jack Kilpatrick's hand found with document.
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 7, Folder 635)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 7, Folder 636)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 7, Folder 637)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 8, Folder 638)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 8, Folder 639)
    Found in proximity: note in Jack Kilpatrick's hand, "Unidentified Coll. III"
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 8, Folder 640)
  - Recto: Medical formula; Verso: Grocery list, 1930 (Box 8, Folder 641)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 8, Folder 642)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 8, Folder 643)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 8, Folder 644)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 8, Folder 645)
  - Bolin, George. Medical formula, undated (Box 8, Folder 646)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 8, Folder 647)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 8, Folder 648)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 8, Folder 649)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 8, Folder 650)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 8, Folder 651)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 8, Folder 652)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 8, Folder 653)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 8, Folder 654)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 8, Folder 655)
    Includes a presumably unrelated annotation, "History II Chapter XXX"
  - Medical formula, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 656)
    Note in Jack Kilpatrick's hand found in proximity suggests date, "Duncan collection 2 1964"
  - Medical formula, 1936 August 21 (Box 8, Folder 657)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 8, Folder 658)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 8, Folder 659)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 8, Folder 660)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 8, Folder 661)
  - Deerinwater, Lucinda. Medical formula, after 1938 February 3 (Box 8, Folder 662)
  - Deerinwater, John. Medical formula, undated (Box 8, Folder 663)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 8, Folder 664)
  - Hat, John. Medical formula notebook, 1922 (Box 8, Folder 665)
  - Medical formula, before 1961 (Box 8, Folder 666)
    Found with note in Jack Kilpatrick's hand "Echota Coll. (found under a stone by a white man 1961 circa)" indicates date.
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 8, Folder 667)
  - Wolf, Arch. Medical formula, undated (Box 8, Folder 668)
    Found with note in Jack Kilpatrick's hand, "Arch Wolf Formula Coll. 1885-1962?"
  - Medical formula, 1920 January (Box 8, Folder 669)
  - Wolf, Arch. Medical formula and journal, 1867 July 22 - 1907 March 31 (Box 8, Folder 670)
    With note in Jack Kilpatrick's hand, "Arch Wolf VII 1907"
  - Wolf, Arch. Medical formula and financial record, 1918 October (Box 8, Folder 671)
    Note in Jack Kilpatrick's hand, "Arch Wolf XI 1918"
  - Wolf, Arch. Medical formula, obituary, and financial record, circa 1924 (Box 8, Folder 672)
    Note in Jack Kilpatrick's hand, "Arch Wolf III 1924"
  - Wolf, Arch. Medical formula, undated (Box 8, Folder 673)
    Note in Jack Kilpatrick's hand, "Arch Wolf IX"
  - Recto: Medical formula; Verso: Financial note, undated (Box 8, Folder 674)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 8, Folder 675)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 8, Folder 676)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 8, Folder 677)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 8, Folder 678)
  - Wosgali. Medical formula, undated (Box 8, Folder 679)
  - Recto: Medical formula; Verso: Financial note, undated (Box 8, Folder 680)
  - Record of births, 1910 October 6 (Box 8, Folder 681)
  - Medical formula, 1915 December 26 (Box 8, Folder 682)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 8, Folder 683)
  - Wolf, Arch. Medical formula, circa 1915 October (Box 8, Folder 684)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 8, Folder 685)
  - Jackson, J.J. Receipt, undated (Box 8, Folder 686)
  - Marion, Tom. Note, 1918 March 11 (Box 8, Folder 687)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 8, Folder 688)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 8, Folder 689)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 8, Folder 690)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 8, Folder 691)
  - Recto: Wolf, Arch. Medical formula; Verso: Financial record, undated (Box 8, Folder 692)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 8, Folder 693)
  - Unidentified note, 1908 July 31 (Box 8, Folder 694)
  - Medical formula, undateed (Box 8, Folder 695)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 8, Folder 696)
  - List; grocery, undated (Box 8, Folder 697)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 8, Folder 698)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 8, Folder 699)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 8, Folder 700)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 8, Folder 701)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 8, Folder 702)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 8, Folder 703)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 8, Folder 704)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 8, Folder 705)
  - Recto: Lord's Prayer; Verso: Medical formula, undated (Box 8, Folder 706)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 8, Folder 707)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 8, Folder 708)
  - Recto: Financial; Verso: Medical formula, 1909 March 27 (Box 8, Folder 709)
  - Medical notebook, undated (Box 8, Folder 710)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 8, Folder 711)
  - Letter, 1917 May 14 (Box 8, Folder 712)
  - Wolf, Arch. Ledger notebook, 1915 (Box 8, Folder 713)
    Accompanied by note in Jack Kilpatrick's hand "Arch Wolf X 1915"
  - Business letter, April 22 (Box 8, Folder 714)
  - Letter or note, undated (Box 8, Folder 715)
  - Siquanida. Medical formula, circa 1963 (Box 8, Folder 716)
    Found with note in Jack Kilpatrick's hand "Doc. by Siquanida Oct. 1963"
  - Medical formula, before 1960 (Box 8, Folder 717)
    Found with note in Jack Kilpatrick's hand; "Molly Sequoyah (Gwalvni) Coll. obtained from her in 1960 by Raymond Fogelson and given to us by him in Jan 1967. He thinks she [?] got them from Sam Wolf."
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 8, Folder 718)
  - Recto: Print advertisement "C.W. Waters"; Verso: Medical formula, undated (Box 8, Folder 719)
  - Business letter, begins "dawisgalvyi sgadugi tsalagi ayeli", undated (Box 8, Folder 720)
  - Medical formula in English, before 1964 (Box 8, Folder 721)
    Found with note in Jack Kilpatrick's hand; "hilvnv kawonu Coll. (obtained at gitayohi March, 1964)"
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 8, Folder 722)
  - List of names, undated (Box 8, Folder 723)
  - Prayer, undated (Box 8, Folder 724)
  - Sawney, Alex. Letter, 1921 December 17 (Box 8, Folder 725)
    Found with note in Jack Kilpatrick's hand; "Duncan Coll. 1 (letters) (Dollie Duncan, Tsuyohvsvi, Dec. 1964) 1921"
  - Death record, obituary, circa 1915 (Box 8, Folder 726)
- Notebook #10: "Uwedasat Vol II 18-24"
  - Kilpatrick Uwedasat notebook cover, "Vol II 18-24", undated (Box 8, Folder 727)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 8, Folder 728)
    Found with note in Jack Kilpatrick's hand: "Uwedasat' Formula Document II (elohi gagusdvdi)." May be compared to texts in Foundations.
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 8, Folder 729)
    Found with note in Jack Kilpatrick's hand; "Uwedasat' Formula Document III (elohi gagusdvdi)." May be compared to texts in Foundations.
  - Recto: Letter in English; Verso: Medical formula, undated (Box 8, Folder 730)
    Found with note in Jack Kilpatrick's hand; "Uwedasat' Formula Document IV (letter from Sec. of Interior to John Ross)".
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 8, Folder 731)
    Found with note in Jack Kilpatrick's hand; "Uwedasat' Formula Document I (elohi gagusdvdi)".
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 8, Folder 732)
    Found with note in Jack Kilpatrick's hand; "Uwedasat' Collection XXII (from stationary tablet; handwriting not of Uwedasadi)"
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 8, Folder 733)
    Found with note in Jack Kilpatrick's hand; "Uwedasat' Collection XVIII (pinned, with demographic data)".
  - Obituary, 1915 May 4 (Box 9, Folder 734)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 9, Folder 735)
  - List of names, undated (Box 9, Folder 736)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 9, Folder 737)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 9, Folder 738)
    Note in Jack Kilpatrick's hand; "Uwedasat' Collection XIX."
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 9, Folder 739)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 9, Folder 740)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 9, Folder 741)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 9, Folder 742)
  - Recto: Medical formula; Verso: Financial note, undated (Box 9, Folder 743)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 9, Folder 744)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 9, Folder 745)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 9, Folder 746)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 9, Folder 747)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 9, Folder 748)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 9, Folder 749)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 9, Folder 750)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 9, Folder 751)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 9, Folder 752)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 9, Folder 753)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 9, Folder 754)
    Found with note in Jack Kilpatrick's hand; "Uwedasat' Collection XX"
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 9, Folder 755)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 9, Folder 756)
    Found with note in Jack Kilpatrick's hand; "Uwedasat' Collection XXI"
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 9, Folder 757)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 9, Folder 758)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 9, Folder 759)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 9, Folder 760)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 9, Folder 761)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 9, Folder 762)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 9, Folder 763)
  - Medical formula, undateed (Box 9, Folder 764)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 9, Folder 765)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 9, Folder 766)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 9, Folder 767)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 9, Folder 768)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 9, Folder 769)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 9, Folder 770)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 9, Folder 771)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 9, Folder 772)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 9, Folder 773)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 9, Folder 774)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 9, Folder 775)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 9, Folder 776)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 9, Folder 777)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 9, Folder 778)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 9, Folder 779)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 9, Folder 780)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 9, Folder 781)
  - Recto: Medical formula; Verso: Text in English about John Wycliffe, undated (Box 9, Folder 782)
  - Recto: Medical formula; Verso: Fragment of a contract in English, circa 1939 November (Box 9, Folder 783)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 9, Folder 784)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 9, Folder 785)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 9, Folder 786)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 9, Folder 787)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 9, Folder 788)
    Found with note in Jack Kilpatrick's hand; "Uwedasat' Collection XXIV."
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 9, Folder 789)
  - Recto: Medical formula; practice writing; Verso: Note in English, undated (Box 9, Folder 790)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 9, Folder 791)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 9, Folder 792)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 9, Folder 793)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 9, Folder 794)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 9, Folder 795)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 9, Folder 796)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 9, Folder 797)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 9, Folder 798)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 9, Folder 799)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 9, Folder 800)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 9, Folder 801)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 9, Folder 802)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 9, Folder 803)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 9, Folder 804)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 9, Folder 805)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 9, Folder 806)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 9, Folder 807)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 9, Folder 808)
  - Medical formula, 1931 November (Box 9, Folder 809)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 9, Folder 810)
  - Medical formula; practice handwriting, undated (Box 9, Folder 811)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 9, Folder 812)
  - Medical formula, circa 1903 (Box 9, Folder 813)
  - Recto: Medical formula; Verso: Cemil, John. Financial note, 1915 (Box 9, Folder 814)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 9, Folder 815)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 9, Folder 816)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 9, Folder 817)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 9, Folder 818)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 9, Folder 819)
  - Uwedasadi (John Campbell). Medical formula, undated (Box 9, Folder 820)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 9, Folder 821)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 9, Folder 822)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 9, Folder 823)
  - Medical formula with financial information, undated (Box 9, Folder 824)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 9, Folder 825)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 9, Folder 826)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 9, Folder 827)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 9, Folder 828)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 9, Folder 829)
  - Historical note, 1930 August 14 (Box 9, Folder 830)
  - Unidentified note, undated (Box 9, Folder 831)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 9, Folder 832)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 10, Folder 833)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 10, Folder 834)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 10, Folder 835)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 10, Folder 836)
  - Recto: Grocery list; Verso: Medical formula, undated (Box 10, Folder 837)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 10, Folder 838)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 10, Folder 839)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 10, Folder 840)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 10, Folder 841)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 10, Folder 842)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 10, Folder 843)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 10, Folder 844)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 10, Folder 845)
  - Obituary, 1898 September 26 (Box 10, Folder 846)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 10, Folder 847)
  - Historical note, 1866 (Box 10, Folder 848)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 10, Folder 849)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 10, Folder 850)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 10, Folder 851)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 10, Folder 852)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 10, Folder 853)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 10, Folder 854)
  - Recto: Medical formula; Verso: Financial note (Box 10, Folder 855)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 10, Folder 856)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 10, Folder 857)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 10, Folder 858)
  - Recto: Medical formula; Verso: Financial note, undated (Box 10, Folder 859)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 10, Folder 860)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 10, Folder 861)
  - Recto: Unidentified note; Verso: List of names, undated (Box 10, Folder 862)
  - Recto: Medical formula; Verso: Financial note, undated (Box 10, Folder 863)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 10, Folder 864)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 10, Folder 865)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 10, Folder 866)
  - Uwedasati. Medical formula, undated (Box 10, Folder 867)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 10, Folder 868)
  - Medical formula, 1945 October 17 (Box 10, Folder 869)
    Found with note in Jack Kilpatrick's hand; "Uwedasat' Collection XXIII (from stationary tablet)".
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 10, Folder 870)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 10, Folder 871)
  - Song, undated (Box 10, Folder 872)
  - Recto: Medical formula; Verso: List of names, undated (Box 10, Folder 873)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 10, Folder 874)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 10, Folder 875)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 10, Folder 876)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 10, Folder 877)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 10, Folder 878)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 10, Folder 879)
  - Medical formula (Box 10, Folder 880)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 10, Folder 881)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 10, Folder 882)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 10, Folder 883)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 10, Folder 884)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 10, Folder 885)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 10, Folder 886)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 10, Folder 887)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 10, Folder 888)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 10, Folder 889)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 10, Folder 890)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 10, Folder 891)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 10, Folder 892)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 10, Folder 893)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 10, Folder 894)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 10, Folder 895)
  - Medical formula, 1926 September (Box 10, Folder 896)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 10, Folder 897)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 10, Folder 898)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 10, Folder 899)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 10, Folder 900)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 10, Folder 902)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 10, Folder 903)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 10, Folder 901)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 10, Folder 904)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 10, Folder 905)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 10, Folder 906)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 10, Folder 907)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 10, Folder 908)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 10, Folder 909)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 10, Folder 910)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 10, Folder 911)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 10, Folder 912)
  - Hymn, undated (Box 10, Folder 913)
  - Prayer, undated (Box 10, Folder 914)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 10, Folder 915)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 10, Folder 916)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 10, Folder 917)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 10, Folder 918)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 10, Folder 919)
  - Recto: Grocery list; Verso: Unidentified note, undated (Box 10, Folder 920)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 10, Folder 921)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 10, Folder 922)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 10, Folder 923)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 10, Folder 924)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 10, Folder 925)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 10, Folder 926)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 10, Folder 927)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 11, Folder 928)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 11, Folder 929)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 11, Folder 930)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 11, Folder 931)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 11, Folder 932)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 11, Folder 933)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 11, Folder 934)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 11, Folder 935)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 11, Folder 936)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 11, Folder 937)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 11, Folder 938)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 11, Folder 939)